export const data = [
    {
        question: "What is Konectar all about?",
        answer: ["Konectar is a business-to-business (B2B) platform that connects farmers directly to business buyers in the fresh produce market, ensuring seamless, fast, and timely transactions.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How does Konectar work?",
        answer: ["Konectar provides a seamless platform where farmers list their produce, and wholesale buyers can browse, negotiate, and purchase directly. The platform facilitates secure transactions, logistics, and payment processing, ensuring a hassle-free experience for both parties",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Who can use Konectar?",
        answer: ["Konectar is designed for: ",
                "- Smallholder farmers looking to expand market access and sell their produce directly to wholesale buyers.",
                "- Wholesale buyers, including retailers, quick service restaurants, hotels, catering Institutions, food processing companies, and exporters, who are looking for a reliable and direct source of high-quality fruits and vegetables.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What are the benefits of using Konectar?",
        answer: [" For Farmers: ",
                "Access to a larger market, fair prices for their produce, and the elimination of middlemen.",
                 "For Buyers: Direct access to fresh, high-quality produce, transparent pricing, and a simplified procurement process.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How does Konectar ensure the quality of produce?",
        answer: ["We have strict guidelines and verification processes in place. Farmers undergo verification before listing their produce, and our quality assurance team checks the produce at multiple stages, ensuring that only fresh and high-quality fruits and vegetables are transacted.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I sign up as a farmer or buyer?",
        answer: ["- For Farmers:" ,
                "Join the Waitlist, fill in your personal and farm information to enjoy early benefits for joining Konectar. Then join the WhatsApp Community for more information.",
                 "-For Buyers:" ,
                 "Once business registration is live; Register on the platform with your business details, browse available produce, and place orders or initiate negotiations with farmers.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How are payments processed on Konectar?",
        answer: ["Konectar uses Escrow Payment method which is a secure payment system, that facilitates transactions between buyers and farmers. Payments are held in escrow until the buyer confirms the receipt of the produce in good condition. This ensures protection for both parties.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },


    {
        question: "What measures are in place to prevent buyers and farmers from transacting offline?",
        answer: ["We are aware that transacting offline could affect the platform's sustainability. To address this, Konectar has implemented several features, such as: ",
                "- Encrypted messaging and communication within the platform. ",
                "- Incentives for loyalty and continuous engagement." ,
                "- Transaction monitoring to identify and address any potential offline dealings.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How does Konectar handle logistics and delivery?",
        answer: ["Konectar partners with verified logistics providers to ensure that the produce is delivered in optimal condition from the farmer to the buyer. Once a transaction is completed, the platform arranges for transportation based on the buyer’s delivery preferences through 3PL partners.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What happens if there is a dispute between the farmer and the buyer?",
        answer: ["Konectar has a dispute resolution process in place. In case of any disagreement regarding the quality or quantity of the produce, both parties can raise a dispute, and our team will mediate to resolve the issue. Payments will remain in escrow until the dispute is resolved.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I cancel an order on Konectar?",
        answer: ["Yes, both farmers and buyers have the option to cancel an order, but this must be done before the produce is dispatched. Cancellations after dispatch may incur penalties, depending on the situation.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Is there any subscription fee to use Konectar?",
        answer: ["Konectar operates on a transaction-based fee model, meaning there is no upfront subscription cost for using the platform. Farmers and buyers only pay a small service fee per transaction.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How does Konectar handle data privacy and security?",
        answer: ["Konectar uses industry-standard encryption and security measures to protect users' data and transactions. Personal information and transaction details are stored securely, and we comply with all relevant data protection regulations.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Does Konectar offer trade financing?",
        answer: ["Yes, through Konpay, Konectar offers trade financing options that allow buyers to purchase on credit and pay over a designated period. This service is provided in collaboration with our financial partners.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How can I contact Konectar for support?",
        answer: ["For any queries or support, you can reach out to our customer service team via the contact form on our website or email us at support@konectar.ng. We also offer live chat support on the app during business hours.",
        ],
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What are the long-term goals of Konectar?",
        answer: ["Konectar aims to revolutionize the agricultural supply chain by providing a fair and transparent marketplace for smallholder farmers and buyers. We plan to expand our platform’s offerings to include more produce categories and introduce innovative services like farm financing, agronomy support, and farm-to-export solutions.",
         ],
          plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    }

]






export const truckdata = [
    {
        question: "How do I register as a logistics provider on Konectar?",
        answer: "Go to Konectar for Logistics Section, then click on the “Sign Up” button, select the logistics provider option, and fill out your company’s details. Once your account is approved, you'll be able to offer delivery and transportation services to buyers and suppliers.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What kind of logistics services can I offer on Konectar?",
        answer: "You can offer various logistics services such as cold storage-as-a-service and cold Trucks/transportation (Reefer Vehicles) for local or nationwide delivery depending on your capabilities.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I receive delivery requests?",
        answer: "Once registered, you'll be able to see requests from suppliers or buyers looking for logistics services in your area. You can accept requests based on availability, capacity, and routes.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What are the requirements for logistics providers?",
        answer: "You must have a registered logistics company, valid licenses, and insurance as required by law. Specific documentation may be needed based on the regions or countries you serve.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How are rates for logistics services determined?",
        answer: "You can set your own rates for transportation services based on factors such as distance, product type, and delivery urgency. Rates can be viewed by buyers and suppliers when choosing a logistics partner.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I handle special shipping requirements like temperature-controlled transport?",
        answer: "If you offer specialized logistics services such as refrigerated or temperature-controlled transport, you can specify this in your profile and set appropriate pricing for these services.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I handle bulk shipments for multiple suppliers or buyers at once?",
        answer: "Yes, you can consolidate shipments from multiple suppliers or buyers as long as it meets your vehicle capacity and delivery route.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },


    {
        question: "How do I track deliveries?",
        answer: "You will be provided with an in-app tracking system where you can update delivery statuses. Buyers and suppliers will also be able to monitor the progress of their deliveries through this system.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What payment methods are supported for logistics services?",
        answer: "Payments for logistics services can be made via bank transfer, credit/debit cards, or digital wallets. Payments will be processed after successful delivery of the goods.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I communicate with buyers and suppliers?",
        answer: "Once a logistics request is accepted, you can use the in-app messaging feature to communicate with buyers or suppliers regarding delivery schedules, routes, or any special instructions.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What if there's a delay or issue during delivery?",
        answer: "If you encounter any delays or issues, you should immediately inform the buyer or supplier through the in-app messaging. Depending on the situation, Konectar's support team can assist in resolving any disputes.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I ensure the safety and quality of goods during transport?",
        answer: "You are expected to follow standard logistics practices to ensure the safety of the products, especially for perishable goods. This includes proper packaging, temperature control (if applicable), and secure handling of the cargo.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I offer insurance for goods in transit?",
        answer: "Yes, if your company provides insurance coverage for goods during transport, you can include this option in your service offerings. You may charge an additional fee for insured deliveries.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What regions can I offer my services in?",
        answer: "You can specify the cities and States in Nigeria where you provide logistics services. Make sure your profile is up-to-date so buyers and suppliers can easily identify your coverage area.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I manage my fleet and drivers through Konectar?",
        answer: "You can manage your fleet and drivers by assigning deliveries to available vehicles and drivers through the platform. This ensures smooth scheduling and tracking for each delivery job.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I get paid for my services?",
        answer: "Payments will be processed through Konectar after you confirm that a delivery has been successfully completed. Payment timelines may vary based on the agreement between you, the buyer, or the supplier.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I offer express or same-day delivery?",
        answer: "Yes, if you have the capacity for express or same-day delivery, you can indicate this on your profile and set pricing accordingly. Buyers and suppliers can select express delivery options if they need urgent services.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I receive feedback from buyers and suppliers?",
        answer: "After completing a delivery, buyers and suppliers can leave ratings and reviews based on their experience. Positive feedback can help improve your reputation and attract more delivery requests.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Are there any fees for logistics providers on Konectar?",
        answer: "Konectar may charge a small service fee for connecting logistics providers with buyers and suppliers. This will be clearly stated during registration and outlined in the terms of service.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },


    {
        question: "What support is available for logistics providers?",
        // answer: () => <div>
        //     <p></p>
        // </div>

        answer: "Konectar offers 24/7 support to logistics providers to assist with any issues related to the platform, deliveries, or payments. You can reach out via our help center or in-app support.",
        plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    }
]


export const buydata = [
    {
        question: "How do I register as a buyer on Konectar?",
        answer: ["To register as a buyer, click on the “Sign Up” button, select the buyer option, and fill in your business details. Once your account is verified, you’ll be able to prompt, browse and purchase from verified farmers that meets your business requirements.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How can I search for specific fruits or vegetables?",
        answer: ["You can use the search bar at the top of the app to find specific fruits, vegetables, or suppliers. You can also use filters to narrow down by product type, location, quality/grade, quantity, price, and more.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I order from multiple suppliers in a single transaction?",
        answer: ["Yes, Konectar allows you to add items from different suppliers to your cart and proceed with a single checkout, streamlining the buying process.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What is the minimum order quantity (MOQ) for purchase?",
        answer: ["Each farmer/supplier sets their own MOQ, which will be clearly indicated on their product listings. You must meet the MOQ for each supplier to complete the purchase.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How are shipping and delivery handled?",
        answer: ["Shipping and delivery are handled by Third Party Logistics providers already integrated into the marketplace. You can view delivery options and estimated times during checkout.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I track my orders?",
        answer: ["Once your order is confirmed, you can track it under the 'Orders' section of your account. We will also notify you via email or in-app notifications about the status of your order.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What payment methods are accepted?",
        answer: ["Konectar uses an Escrow payment service to ensure secure transactions between farmers and wholesale buyers. This method ensures that payments are held by a trusted third party (the platform) until both parties fulfill their obligations—farmers deliver produce to meet the buyer’s requirements, and buyers confirm the delivery.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },


    {
        question: "How does the Escrow Payment work?",
        answer: ["Once the buyer and user reach an agreement, they proceed to set up the escrow payment arrangement.",
            
                "- The user selects the escrow payment system on Konectar and specifies the agreed-upon terms, including payment amounts, milestones, and delivery timelines." ,
                "- The buyer reviews and accepts the escrow terms, and the funds are deposited into the escrow account.",
        
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I negotiate prices with suppliers?",
        answer: ["Yes, some suppliers may allow price negotiations, especially for bulk orders. You can use the messaging feature to communicate directly with the supplier and discuss pricing.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How does Konectar ensure quality delivery to Buyers?",
        answer: ["Konectar ensures the quality delivery of produce to Buyers by these measures;", 
                "- Collection Centers or Packinghouses for Quality Checks:", 
                "Farmers are required to first transport their produce to designated Collection Centers or Packinghouses. Here, the produce undergoes thorough quality inspections to ensure it meets the specific requirements and expectations of the buyers, such as size, freshness, and other quality standards.", 
                "- Standardized Grading and Sorting:", 
                "At the Collection Centers, produce is graded and sorted based on industry-standard criteria. This helps ensure consistency in quality and that only the best products reach the buyers.", 
                "- Escrow Payment System:",
                "Konectar escrow payment service provides an additional quality assurance layer. The payment is held by the platform until the buyer confirms the receipt of goods in satisfactory condition.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What if there is an issue with the quality of products received?",
        answer: ["Konectar has a buyer protection policy. If you receive products that do not meet the agreed-upon quality, you can report the issue through the app and request a resolution within a specified period.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Are there any fees for buyers on Konectar?",
        answer: ["No, registering as a buyer and making purchases on Konectar is free. However, some suppliers may charge for delivery or additional services, which will be displayed during checkout.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I communicate with suppliers?",
        answer: ["You can contact suppliers directly through the in-app messaging system. This allows you to inquire about products, negotiate prices, or ask questions regarding orders.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Can I repeat a previous order?",
        answer: ["Yes, you can easily reorder by going to your order history and selecting the “Reorder” option for any past transactions.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "How do I leave reviews or feedback for suppliers?",
        answer: ["After completing a purchase, you will have the option to leave a review based on your experience. You can rate the supplier and provide comments on product quality and service.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "What regions does Konectar serve?",
        answer: ["Konectar connects buyers and suppliers Nationwide, but we are currently servicing farmers and wholesale buyers in Lagos, Ogun, Oyo, Ekiti, Osun, Edo, Delta and Rivers State. However the availability of certain products may depend on regional supply and shipping capabilities.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

    {
        question: "Is there a way to favorite suppliers or products?",
        answer: ["Yes, you can favorite suppliers or products by clicking the heart icon on their listings. This allows you to easily access your preferred suppliers or products in the future.",
        ],
            plus: "+",
        minus: "-"
    },

]